<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Dublin Pub Finder</string>
    <string name="qwhatpub">What pub are you looking for?</string>
    <string name="findpub">Find pub</string>
    <string name="copyright">© Tony Blake 2016</string>
    <string name="pubnotfound">Pub not found</string>
    <string name="errorfindingpub">Error finding pub</string>
    <string name="errorretrievingpubimage">"Error retrieving pub image"</string>
    <string name="directions">Directions</string>

    <string name="alfie_byrnes">Alfie Byrnes</string>
    <string name="alfie_byrnes_address">Earlsfort Terrace, Dublin 2</string>
    <string name="alfie_byrnes_directions">From College Green (Trinity College), turn left and walk down Nassau Street. Take the first right turn and walk all the way up Dawson Street. At the top of Dawson Street, turn left and walk around St. Stephen\'s Green. Then, turn left onto Lesson Street Lower. You will see Alfie Byrne\'s a few feet up this street on the right.</string>

    <string name="bailey_bar">Bailey Bar</string>
    <string name="bailey_bar_address">2 Duke St, Dublin 2</string>
    <string name="bailey_bar_directions">From College Green (Trinity College), turn left and walk up Grafton Street. Take the first left turn onto Duke Street. You will see the Bailey Bar on the left.</string>

    <string name="bruxelles">Bruxelles</string>
    <string name="bruxelles_address">7 Harry St, Dublin 2</string>
    <string name="bruxelles_directions">From College Green (Trinity College), turn left and walk over to Grafton Street. Walk up Grafton Street and take the third right turn onto Harry Street. You will see Bruxelles on the right.</string>

    <string name="capitol_bar">Capitol Bar</string>
    <string name="capitol_bar_address">1 Aungier St, Dublin 2</string>
    <string name="capitol_bar_directions">From College Green (Trinity College), walk straight up Dame Street. Take the third left turn onto South Great George\'s Street. Walk up this street until you come to Aungier Street. You will see the Capitol Bar on the left corner.</string>

    <string name="cassidys">Cassidys</string>
    <string name="cassidys_address">27 Westmoreland St, Dublin 2</string>
    <string name="cassidys_directions">From O\' Connell Street, walk over O\' Connell bridge and continue straight onto Westmoreland Street. You will see Cassidys a few feet up this street on the left.</string>

    <string name="doyles">Doyles</string>
    <string name="doyles_address">9 College St, Dublin 2</string>
    <string name="doyles_directions">From O\' Connell Street, walk over O\' Connell bridge and continue straight onto D\'Olier Street. Walk up to the top of this street and you will see Doyle\'s on the right.</string>

    <string name="east_side_tavern">East Side Tavern</string>
    <string name="east_side_tavern_address">104 Leeson Street Lower, Dublin 2</string>
    <string name="east_side_tavern_directions">From College Green (Trinity College), turn left and walk down Nassau Street. Take the first right turn and walk all the way up Dawson Street. Then, turn left and walk around St. Stephen\'s Green. Turn left onto Leeson Street Lower and you will immediately see the East Side Tavern.</string>

    <string name="fibber_magee">Fibber Magees</string>
    <string name="fibber_magee_address">80 Parnel Street, Dublin 1.</string>
    <string name="fibber_magee_directions">From O\'Connell Street, walk past the Savoy Cinema and continue on down to Parnell Street and turn right. Fibber Magees is just a few feet away.</string>

    <string name="hartigans">Hartigans</string>
    <string name="hartigans_address">100 Leeson Street Lower, Dublin 2</string>
    <string name="hartigans_directions">From College Green (Trinity College), turn left and walk down Nassau Street. Take the first right turn and walk all the way up Dawson Street. Then, turn left and walk around St. Stephen\'s Green. Turn left onto Leeson Street Lower and you will see Hartigan\'s a few feet up the street.</string>

    <string name="hogans">Hogans</string>
    <string name="hogans_address">35 South Great Georges Street, Dublin 2</string>
    <string name="hogans_directions">From College Green (Trinity College), walk straight up Dame Street. Take the third left turn and walk up South Great George\'s Street. Continue on up this street, past Exchequer Street, and you\'ll soon see Hogan\'s on the left.</string>

    <string name="jj_smyths">J.J. Smyths</string>
    <string name="jj_smyths_address">12 Aungier St, Dublin 2</string>
    <string name="jj_smyths_directions">From College Green (Trinity College), walk straight up Dame Street. Take the third left turn and walk up South Great George\'s Street. Continue on up this street and onto Aungier Street. J.J. Smyth\'s is on the first left corner of this street.</string>

    <string name="john_kehoe">John Kehoes</string>
    <string name="john_kehoe_address">9 South Anne Street, Dublin 2</string>
    <string name="john_kehoe_directions">From College Green (Trinity College), turn left and walk up Grafton Street. Take the third right turn onto South Anne Street. You will see John Kehoe\'s on the left corner.</string>

    <string name="jw_sweetman">J.W. Sweetman</string>
    <string name="jw_sweetman_address">1 Burgh Quay, Dublin 2</string>
    <string name="jw_sweetman_directions">From O\'Connell Street, walk over O\'Connell bridge and turn left onto Burgh Quay. J.W. Sweetman is just a few steps away.</string>

    <string name="nearys">Nearys</string>
    <string name="nearys_address">1 Chatham Street, Dublin 2</string>
    <string name="nearys_directions">From College Green (Trinity College), turn left and walk up Grafton Street. Take the fourth right turn onto Chatham Street. You will see Neary\'s on the left.</string>

    <string name="odonoghues">O Donoghues</string>
    <string name="odonoghues_address">15 Merrion Row, Dublin 2</string>
    <string name="odonoghues_directions">From College Green (Trinity College), turn left and walk down Nassau Street. Take the first right turn and walk all the way up Dawson Street. Then, turn left at St. Stephen\'s Green and continue on to Merrion Row. You will then see O\' Donoghue\'s on the right.</string>

    <string name="porterhouse_central">Porterhouse Central</string>
    <string name="porterhouse_central_address">45 Nassau Street, Dublin 2</string>
    <string name="porterhouse_central_directions">From College Green (Trinity College), turn left and walk up Nassau Street. You will see Porterhouse Central a few feet up on the right.</string>

    <string name="river_bar">River Bar</string>
    <string name="river_bar_address">1 Burgh Quay, Dublin 2</string>
    <string name="river_bar_directions">From O\' Connell Street, walk over O\' Connell bridge and turn left onto Burgh Quay. You will see the River Bar on the right.</string>

    <string name="synnotts">Synnotts</string>
    <string name="synnotts_address">South King Street, Dublin 2</string>
    <string name="synnotts_directions">From College Green (Trinity College), turn left and walk up Grafton Street. Take the last right turn onto South King Street. You will see Synnott\'s on the left.</string>

    <string name="the_duke">The Duke</string>
    <string name="the_duke_address">8 Duke St, Dublin 2</string>
    <string name="the_duke_directions">From College Green (Trinity College), turn left and walk up Grafton Street. Take the first left turn onto Duke Street. You will see The Duke on the left.</string>

    <string name="the_globe_bar">The Globe Bar</string>
    <string name="the_globe_bar_address">11 South Great Georges Street. Dublin 2</string>
    <string name="the_globe_bar_directions">From College Green (Trinity College), walk straight up Dame Street. Take the third left turn onto South Great George\'s Street. Walk a few feet up this street and you will see The Globe Bar on the left.</string>

    <string name="the_grafton_lounge">The Grafton Lounge</string>
    <string name="the_grafton_lounge_address">2 Duke Lane Upper, Dublin 2</string>
    <string name="the_grafton_lounge_directions">From College Green (Trinity College), turn left and walk up Grafton Street. Take the first left turn onto Duke Street. Then, take the first right turn onto Duke Lane Upper. You will see The Grafton Lounge a few feet down on the left.</string>

    <string name="the_long_hall">The Long Hall</string>
    <string name="the_long_hall_address">51 South Great George\'s Street, Dublin 2</string>
    <string name="the_long_hall_directions">From College Green (Trinity College), walk straight up Dame Street. Take the third left turn and walk up South Great George\'s Street. The Long Hall is just beyond Fade Street.</string>

    <string name="the_stags_head">The Stags Head</string>
    <string name="the_stags_head_address">1 Dame Court, Dublin 2</string>
    <string name="the_stags_head_directions">From O\'Connell Street, walk over O\'Connell bridge and continue straight onto D\'Olier Street. At the end of this street, take a right up to College Green. From there, walk up Dame Street and turn left onto Trinity Street. Turn right onto Dame Lane and you\'ll see The Stag\'s Head up on the left.</string>

    <string name="the_temple_bar">The Temple Bar</string>
    <string name="the_temple_bar_address">47 Temple Bar, Dublin 2.</string>
    <string name="the_temple_bar_directions">From O\'Connell Street, walk over O\'Connell bridge and turn right onto Aston Quay. Walk straight until you come to the Ha\'penny bridge. Then, turn left and walk under Merchant Arch. You are now in Temple Bar, the Temple Bar is down the cobblestones on the right.</string>

</resources>
