<resources>

    <string name="app_name">Dublin Pub Finder</string>
    <string name="enter">Enter</string>
    <string name="copyright">© Tony Blake 2016</string>

    <string name="qtypepub">Q1: What type of pub are you looking for?</string>
    <string name="traditional">Traditional Irish pub</string>
    <string name="modern">Modern pub</string>
    <string name="qsidecity">Q2: What side of the city are you on?</string>
    <string name="northside">Northside</string>
    <string name="southside">Southside</string>
    <string name="qlivemusic">Q3: Are you looking for a pub with live music?*</string>
    <string name="yes">Yes</string>
    <string name="no">No</string>
    <string name="qcraftbeer">Q4: Are you looking for a pub that serves craft beer?</string>
    <string name="qlatepub">Q5: Are you looking for a pub that stays open late?</string>
    <string name="find_pub">Find pub</string>
    <string name="live_music_note"><i>*Live music only on certain nights</i></string>

    <string name="please_select_pub_type">Please select pub type</string>
    <string name="please_select_your_location">Please select which side of the city you are on</string>
    <string name="please_select_live_music">Please select whether or not you want live music</string>
    <string name="please_select_craft_beer">Please select whether or not you want craft beer</string>
    <string name="please_select_late_pub">Please select whether or not you want a pub that stays open late</string>

    <string name="getMapLocation">Get Map Location</string>
    <string name="no_pubs_match_your_search">No pubs match your search. Please try again</string>
    <string name="errorfindingpub">Error finding pub</string>
    <string name="errorretrievingpubimage">"Error retrieving pub image"</string>

    <string name="against_the_grain">Against The Grain</string>
    <string name="against_the_grain_address">11 Wexford Street, Dublin 2</string>
    <string name="against_the_grain_side_of_city">Southside</string>
    <string name="against_the_grain_latitude">53.337230</string>
    <string name="against_the_grain_longitude">-6.265333</string>
    <string name="against_the_grain_pub_type">Modern</string>
    <string name="against_the_grain_live_music">No</string>
    <string name="against_the_grain_craft_beer">Yes</string>
    <string name="against_the_grain_late_pub">No</string>

    <string name="alfie_byrnes">Alfie Byrnes</string>
    <string name="alfie_byrnes_address">Earlsfort Terrace, Dublin 2</string>
    <string name="alfie_byrnes_directions">From College Green (Trinity College), turn to face Dame Street. Turn left and walk down Nassau Street. Take the first right turn and walk all the way up Dawson Street. At the top of Dawson Street, turn left and walk around St. Stephen\'s Green. Then, turn left onto Lesson Street Lower. You will see Alfie Byrne\'s a few feet up this street on the right.</string>

    <string name="anseo">Anseo</string>
    <string name="anseo_address">18 Camden Street Lower, Dublin 2</string>
    <string name="anseo_side_of_city">Southside</string>
    <string name="anseo_latitude">53.335215</string>
    <string name="anseo_longitude">-6.265121</string>
    <string name="anseo_pub_type">Modern</string>
    <string name="anseo_live_music">Yes</string>
    <string name="anseo_craft_beer">Yes</string>
    <string name="anseo_late_pub">No</string>

    <string name="bad_bobs">Bad Bobs</string>
    <string name="bad_bobs_address">35 Essex Street East, Dublin 2</string>
    <string name="bad_bobs_directions">From O\'Connell Street, walk over O\'Connell bridge and turn right onto Aston Quay. Walk straight until you come to the Ha\'penny bridge. Continue on straight until you come to the Millennium bridge. Then, turn left onto Eustace Street and turn right onto Essex Street East. You will see Bad Bob\'s on the left hand corner.</string>

    <string name="break_for_the_border">Break For The Border</string>
    <string name="break_for_the_border_address">Stephen Street Lower, Dublin 2</string>
    <string name="break_for_the_border_directions">From College Green (Trinity College), turn to face Dame Street. Turn left and walk up Grafton Street. Take the first right turn onto Wicklow Street and then take the second left turn onto William Street South. Walk all the way up this street and take the last right turn. You will see Break For The Border on the left.</string>

    <string name="bruxelles">Bruxelles</string>
    <string name="bruxelles_address">7 Harry St, Dublin 2</string>
    <string name="bruxelles_directions">From College Green (Trinity College), turn to face Dame Street. Turn left and walk over to Grafton Street. Walk up Grafton Street and take the third right turn onto Harry Street. You will see Bruxelles on the right.</string>

    <string name="buskers">Buskers</string>
    <string name="buskers_address">13 Fleet St, Dublin 2</string>
    <string name="buskers_directions">From O\' Connell Street, walk over O\' Connell bridge and continue straight onto Westmoreland Street. Take the first right turn onto Fleet Street. Walk a few feet up this street and you will see Busker\'s on the right.</string>

    <string name="café_en_seine">Café en Seine</string>
    <string name="café_en_seine_address">40 Dawson Street, Dublin 2</string>
    <string name="café_en_seine_directions">From College Green (Trinity College), turn to face Dame Street. Turn left and walk around Trinity College. Take the first right turn onto Dawson Street. Walk up this street, past Duke Street and then past Anne Street South. You will see Café en Seine on the right.</string>

    <string name="cassidys">Cassidys</string>
    <string name="cassidys_address">27 Westmoreland St, Dublin 2</string>
    <string name="cassidys_directions">From O\' Connell Street, walk over O\' Connell bridge and continue straight onto Westmoreland Street. You will see Cassidys a few feet up this street on the left.</string>

    <string name="devitts">Devitts</string>
    <string name="devitts_address">78 Lower Camden Street, Dublin 2</string>
    <string name="devitts_directions">From College Green (Trinity College), turn to face Dame Street. Walk straight up Dame Street and take the third left turn onto South Great George\'s Street. Walk straight up this street and continue onto Aungier Street. Walk straight up this street and continue onto Wexford Street. Continue straight onto Camden Street and you will see Devitt\'s on the right.</string>

    <string name="doheny_and_nesbitts">Doheny And Nesbitts</string>
    <string name="doheny_and_nesbitts_address">5 Baggot Street Lower, Dublin 2</string>
    <string name="doheny_and_nesbitts_directions">From College Green (Trinity College), turn to face Dame Street. Turn left and walk around Trinity College. Take the first right turn and walk all the way up Dawson Street. Then, turn left at St. Stephen\'s Green and continue on to Merrion Row. Walk up this street and continue onto Baggot Street Lower. You will see Doheny And Nesbitt\'s on the left.</string>

    <string name="doyles">Doyles</string>
    <string name="doyles_address">9 College St, Dublin 2</string>
    <string name="doyles_directions">From O\' Connell Street, walk over O\' Connell bridge and continue straight onto D\'Olier Street. Walk up to the top of this street and you will see Doyle\'s on the right.</string>

    <string name="fibber_magees">Fibber Magees</string>
    <string name="fibber_magees_address">80 Parnel Street, Dublin 1</string>
    <string name="fibber_magees_directions">From O\'Connell Street, walk past the Savoy Cinema and continue on down to Parnell Street and turn right. Fibber Magees is just a few feet away.</string>

    <string name="fitzgeralds">Fitzgeralds</string>
    <string name="fitzgeralds_address">22 Aston Quay, Dublin 2</string>
    <string name="fitzgeralds_directions">From O\'Connell Street, walk over O\'Connell bridge and turn right onto Aston Quay. Walk a few feet up this street and you will see Fitzgerald\'s on the left.</string>

    <string name="fitzsimons">Fitzsimons</string>
    <string name="fitzsimons_address">21 Wellington Quay, Temple Bar, Dublin 2</string>
    <string name="fitzsimons_directions">From O\'Connell Street, walk over O\'Connell bridge and turn right onto Aston Quay. Walk straight until you come to the Ha\'penny bridge. Then, turn left and walk under Merchant Arch. You are now in Temple Bar, Fitzsimon\'s is down the cobblestones on the right.</string>

    <string name="flannerys">Flannerys</string>
    <string name="flannerys_address">6 Camden Street Lower, Dublin 2</string>
    <string name="flannerys_directions">From College Green (Trinity College), turn to face Dame Street. Walk straight up Dame Street and take the third left turn onto South Great George\'s Street. Walk straight up this street and continue onto Aungier Street. Walk straight up this street and continue onto Wexford Street. Continue straight onto Camden Street and you will see Flannery\'s on the left.</string>

    <string name="four_dame_lane">4 Dame Lane</string>
    <string name="four_dame_lane_address">4 Dame Lane, Dublin 2</string>
    <string name="four_dame_lane_directions">From College Green (Trinity College), turn to face Dame Street. Walk up Dame Street and take the second left turn onto Trinity Street. Take the first right turn onto Dame Lane. You will see 4 Dame Lane on the left.</string>

    <string name="grogans">Grogans</string>
    <string name="grogans_address">15 South William Street, Dublin 2</string>
    <string name="grogans_directions">From College Green (Trinity College), turn to face Dame Street. Turn left and walk up Grafton Street. Take the first right turn onto Wicklow Street and then take the second left turn onto William Street South. Walk a few feet up this street and you will see Grogan\'s on the left.</string>

    <string name="hartigans">Hartigans</string>
    <string name="hartigans_address">100 Leeson Street Lower, Dublin 2</string>
    <string name="hartigans_directions">From College Green (Trinity College), turn to face Dame Street. Turn left and walk down Nassau Street. Take the first right turn and walk all the way up Dawson Street. Then, turn left and walk around St. Stephen\'s Green. Turn left onto Leeson Street Lower and you will see Hartigan\'s a few feet up the street.</string>

    <string name="hogans">Hogans</string>
    <string name="hogans_address">35 South Great Georges Street, Dublin 2</string>
    <string name="hogans_directions">From College Green (Trinity College), walk straight up Dame Street. Take the third left turn and walk up South Great George\'s Street. Continue on up this street, past Exchequer Street, and you\'ll soon see Hogan\'s on the left.</string>

    <string name="jj_smyths">J.J. Smyths</string>
    <string name="jj_smyths_address">12 Aungier St, Dublin 2</string>
    <string name="jj_smyths_directions">From College Green (Trinity College), walk straight up Dame Street. Take the third left turn and walk up South Great George\'s Street. Continue on up this street and onto Aungier Street. J.J. Smyth\'s is on the first left corner of this street.</string>

    <string name="john_kehoes">John Kehoes</string>
    <string name="john_kehoes_address">9 South Anne Street, Dublin 2</string>
    <string name="john_kehoes_directions">From College Green (Trinity College), turn to face Dame Street. Turn left and walk up Grafton Street. Take the third right turn onto South Anne Street. You will see John Kehoe\'s on the left corner.</string>

    <string name="jw_sweetmans">J.W. Sweetmans</string>
    <string name="jw_sweetmans_address">1 Burgh Quay, Dublin 2</string>
    <string name="jw_sweetmans_directions">From O\'Connell Street, walk over O\'Connell bridge and turn left onto Burgh Quay. J.W. Sweetman is just a few steps away.</string>

    <string name="kennedys">Kennedys</string>
    <string name="kennedys_address">31 Westland Row, Dublin 2</string>
    <string name="kennedys_directions">From College Green (Trinity College), turn to face Dame Street. Turn left and walk around Trinity College. Continue straight onto Nassau Street, then onto Leinster Street South. At the end of this street, turn left onto Lincoln Place. You will see Kennedy\'s at the end of this street on the corner.</string>

    <string name="lanigans">Lanigans</string>
    <string name="lanigans_address">10 Eden Quay, Dublin 1</string>
    <string name="lanigans_directions">From O\'Connell Street (the Spire), turn to face O\' Connell bridge and walk straight. Take the last left turn onto Eden Quay. Walk a few feet up this street and you will see Lanigan\'s on the left.</string>

    <string name="lagoona">Lagoona</string>
    <string name="lagoona_address">Mayor Street Lower, IFSC, Dublin 1</string>
    <string name="lagoona_directions">From O\'Connell Street (the Spire), turn to face O\' Connell bridge and walk straight. Take the second left turn onto Abbey Street Lower. Walk all the way up this street and around the bus garage (Busáras). Turn right and walk into the IFSC. Walk straight past the Harbourmaster and on to Mayor Street Lower. You will see Lagoona on the left.</string>

    <string name="mulligans">Mulligans</string>
    <string name="mulligans_address">8 Poolbeg Street, Dublin 2</string>
    <string name="mulligans_directions">From O\' Connell Street, walk over O\' Connell bridge and turn left onto Burgh Quay. Walk up this street and take the first right turn onto Hawkins Street. Then, take the first left turn onto Poolbeg Street. You will see Mulligan\'s a few feet up this street on the left.</string>

    <string name="nearys">Nearys</string>
    <string name="nearys_address">1 Chatham Street, Dublin 2</string>
    <string name="nearys_directions">From College Green (Trinity College), turn to face Dame Street. Turn left and walk up Grafton Street. Take the fourth right turn onto Chatham Street. You will see Neary\'s on the left.</string>

    <string name="o_donoghues">O Donoghues</string>
    <string name="o_donoghues_address">15 Merrion Row, Dublin 2</string>
    <string name="o_donoghues_directions">From College Green (Trinity College), turn to face Dame Street. Turn left and walk around Trinity College. Take the first right turn and walk all the way up Dawson Street. Then, turn left at St. Stephen\'s Green and continue on to Merrion Row. You will then see O\' Donoghue\'s on the right.</string>

    <string name="o_reillys">O Reillys</string>
    <string name="o_reillys_address">Tara Street Station, 2 Poolbeg Street, Dublin 2</string>
    <string name="o_reillys_directions">From O\' Connell Street, walk over O\' Connell bridge and turn left onto Burgh Quay. Continue straight onto George\'s Quay. Walk past Tara Street Station and turn right onto Luke Street. You will see O\' Reillys a few feet down this street on the right.</string>

    <string name="peters_pub">Peters Pub</string>
    <string name="peters_pub_address">William Street South, Dublin 2</string>
    <string name="peters_pub_directions">From College Green (Trinity College), turn to face Dame Street. Turn left and walk up Grafton Street. Take the first right turn onto Wicklow Street and then take the second left turn onto William Street South. Walk all the way up this street and you will see Peter\'s Pub on the left hand corner.</string>

    <string name="p_macs">P. Macs</string>
    <string name="p_macs_address">30 Stephen Street Lower, Dublin 2</string>
    <string name="p_macs_directions">From College Green (Trinity College), turn to face Dame Street. Turn left and walk up Grafton Street. Take the first right turn onto Wicklow Street and then take the second left turn onto William Street South. Walk all the way up this street and take the last right turn. You will see P. Mac\'s on the left hand corner.</string>

    <string name="robert_reids">Robert Reids</string>
    <string name="robert_reids_address">19 Store St, Dublin 1</string>
    <string name="robert_reids_directions">From O\'Connell Street (the Spire), turn to face O\' Connell bridge and walk straight. Take the second left turn onto Abbey Street Lower. Walk up this street and take the second left turn onto Gardiner Street South. Take the first right turn and walk down Frenchman\'s Lane. You will see Robert Reid\'s at the end on the left.</string>

    <string name="ryans">Ryans</string>
    <string name="ryans_address">92 Camden Street Lower, Dublin 2</string>
    <string name="ryans_directions">From College Green (Trinity College), turn to face Dame Street. Walk straight up Dame Street and take the third left turn onto South Great George\'s Street. Walk straight up this street and continue onto Aungier Street. Walk straight up this street and continue onto Wexford Street. Continue straight onto Camden Street and you will see Ryan\'s on the right corner.</string>

    <string name="searsons">Searsons</string>
    <string name="searsons_address">44 Baggot Street Upper, Dublin 4</string>
    <string name="searsons_directions">From College Green (Trinity College), turn to face Dame Street. Turn left and walk around Trinity College. Take the first right turn and walk all the way up Dawson Street. Then, turn left at St. Stephen\'s Green and continue on to Merrion Row. Walk up this street and continue onto Baggot Street Lower. At the end of this street, walk over the bridge and continue onto Baggot Street Upper. You will see Searson\'s at the end of this street on the left.</string>

    <string name="sheehans">Sheehans</string>
    <string name="sheehans_address">17 Chatham St, Dublin 2</string>
    <string name="sheehans_directions">From College Green (Trinity College), turn to face Dame Street. Turn left and walk up Grafton Street. Take the fourth right turn onto Chatham Street. Walk a few feet up this street and you will see Sheehan\'s on the right hand corner.</string>

    <string name="sin_é">Sin É</string>
    <string name="sin_é_address">15 Ormond Quay Upper, Dublin 1</string>
    <string name="sin_é_directions">From O\' Connell Street, walk towards O\' Connell bridge and turn right onto Bachelors Walk. Walk straight up this street and continue on past the Ha\'penny bridge onto Ormond Quay Lower. Continue straight, past the Millenium bridge, then past Grattan bridge onto Ormond Quay Upper. You will see Sin É a few feet up on the right.</string>

    <string name="synnotts">Synnotts</string>
    <string name="synnotts_address">South King Street, Dublin 2</string>
    <string name="synnotts_directions">From College Green (Trinity College), turn to face Dame Street. Turn left and walk up Grafton Street. Take the last right turn onto South King Street. You will see Synnott\'s on the left.</string>

    <string name="the_auld_dubliner">The Auld Dubliner</string>
    <string name="the_auld_dubliner_address">24 Temple Bar, Dublin 2</string>
    <string name="the_auld_dubliner_directions">From O\'Connell Street, walk over O\'Connell bridge and continue straight onto Westmoreland Street. Walk up this street and take the first right turn onto Fleet Street. Walk up this street and you will soon see The Auld Dubliner on the left hand corner.</string>

    <string name="the_bank">The Bank</string>
    <string name="the_bank_address">20 College Green, Dublin 2</string>
    <string name="the_bank_directions">From O\' Connell Street, walk over O\' Connell bridge and continue straight up Westmoreland Street. Walk to the end of this street and onto College Green (Trinity College). Turn to face Dame Street and you will see The Bank a few feet up on the left hand side.</string>

    <string name="the_bankers">The Bankers</string>
    <string name="the_bankers_address">Trinity Street, Dublin 2</string>
    <string name="the_bankers_directions">From College Green (Trinity College), turn to face Dame Street. Walk up this street and take the second left turn onto Trinity Street. Walk a few feet up this street and you will see the Banker\'s on the right hand corner</string>

    <string name="the_bar_with_no_name">The Bar With No Name</string>
    <string name="the_bar_with_no_name_address">3 Fade Street, Dublin 2</string>
    <string name="the_bar_with_no_name_directions">From College Green (Trinity College), turn to face Dame Street. Walk up this street and take the third left turn and walk up South Great George\'s Street. Take the third left turn onto Fade Street. You will see The Bar With No Name a few feet up on the right.</string>

    <string name="the_bailey_bar">The Bailey Bar</string>
    <string name="the_bailey_bar_address">2 Duke St, Dublin 2</string>
    <string name="the_bailey_bar_directions">From College Green (Trinity College), turn to face Dame Street. Turn left and walk up Grafton Street. Take the first left turn onto Duke Street. You will see the Bailey Bar on the left.</string>

    <string name="the_bison_bar">The Bison Bar</string>
    <string name="the_bison_bar_address">11 Wellington Quay, Dublin 2</string>
    <string name="the_bison_bar_directions">From O\' Connell Street, walk over O\' Connell bridge and turn right onto Aston Quay. Walk straight along the Quays, past the Ha\'penny bridge. Continue on straight, past the Millenium bridge. You will soon see The Bison Bar on the left.</string>

    <string name="the_brew_dock">The Brew Dock</string>
    <string name="the_brew_dock_address">1 Amiens Street, Dublin 1</string>
    <string name="the_brew_dock_directions">From O\' Connell Street (the Spire), turn to face O\' Connell bridge and walk straight. Take the second left turn onto Abbey Street Lower. Walk all the way up this street and around the bus garage (Busáras). You will see The Brew Dock straight in front of you.</string>

    <string name="the_bull_and_castle">The Bull And Castle</string>
    <string name="the_bull_and_castle_address">5 Lord Edward Street, Dublin 8</string>
    <string name="the_bull_and_castle_directions">From College Green (Trinity College), turn to face Dame Street. Walk up the entire length of this street, past City Hall, and continue straight onto Lord Edward Street. You will see The Bull And Castle at the end of this street on the left corner.</string>

    <string name="the_camden_exchange">The Camden Exchange</string>
    <string name="the_camden_exchange_address">72 Camden Street Lower, Dublin 2</string>
    <string name="the_camden_exchange_directions">From College Green (Trinity College), turn to face Dame Street. Walk straight up Dame Street and take the third left turn onto South Great George\'s Street. Walk straight up this street and continue onto Aungier Street. Walk straight up this street and continue onto Wexford Street. Continue straight onto Camden Street and you will see The Camden Exchange on the right.</string>

    <string name="the_capitol_bar">The Capitol Bar</string>
    <string name="the_capitol_bar_address">1 Aungier St, Dublin 2</string>
    <string name="the_capitol_bar_directions">From College Green (Trinity College), walk straight up Dame Street. Take the third left turn onto South Great George\'s Street. Walk up this street until you come to Aungier Street. You will see the Capitol Bar on the left corner.</string>

    <string name="the_celt">The Celt</string>
    <string name="the_celt_address">81 Talbot Street, Dublin 1</string>
    <string name="the_celt_directions">From O\' Connell Street (the Spire), turn to face O\' Connell bridge and turn left onto Earl Street North. Walk up this street and continue on to Talbot Street. Walk down Talbot Street and you will soon see The Celt on the right.</string>

    <string name="the_church">The Church</string>
    <string name="the_church_address">Jervis Street, Dublin 1</string>
    <string name="the_church_directions">From O\' Connell Street (the Spire), turn to face O\' Connell bridge and turn right onto Henry Street. Walk all the way up this street and you will see The Church on the left hand corner.</string>

    <string name="the_czech_inn">The Czech Inn</string>
    <string name="the_czech_inn_address">Essex gate, Temple Bar, Dublin 8</string>
    <string name="the_czech_inn_directions">From O\'Connell Street, walk over O\'Connell bridge and turn right onto Aston Quay. Walk straight until you come to the Ha\'penny bridge. Continue on straight until you come to the Millennium bridge. Then, turn left onto Eustace Street and turn right onto Essex Street. Walk up this street and you will see The Czech Inn on the right hand corner.</string>

    <string name="the_dame_tavern">The Dame Tavern</string>
    <string name="the_dame_tavern_address">18 Dame Court, Dublin 2</string>
    <string name="the_dame_tavern_directions">From College Green (Trinity College), turn to face Dame Street. Walk up this street and take the second left turn onto Trinity Street. Then, take the first right turn onto Dame Lane. Walk up this lane and you will see Dame Tavern on the left hand corner.</string>

    <string name="the_dawson_lounge">The Dawson Lounge</string>
    <string name="the_dawson_lounge_address">25 Dawson Street, Dublin 2</string>
    <string name="the_dawson_lounge_directions">From College Green (Trinity College), turn to face Dame Street. Turn left and walk around Trinity College. Take the first right turn onto Dawson Street. Walk all the way up this street and you will see The Dawson Lounge on the right.</string>

    <string name="the_drury_buildings">The Drury Buildings</string>
    <string name="the_drury_buildings_address">55 Drury Street, Dublin 2</string>
    <string name="the_drury_buildings_directions">From College Green (Trinity College), turn to face Dame Street. Walk up this street and take the third left turn and walk up South Great George\'s Street. Take the third left turn onto Fade Street. Walk to the end of this street and you will see The Drury Buildings across the road.</string>

    <string name="the_duke">The Duke</string>
    <string name="the_duke_address">8 Duke St, Dublin 2</string>
    <string name="the_duke_directions">From College Green (Trinity College), turn to face Dame Street. Turn left and walk up Grafton Street. Take the first left turn onto Duke Street. You will see The Duke on the left.</string>

    <string name="the_east_side_tavern">The East Side Tavern</string>
    <string name="the_east_side_tavern_address">104 Leeson Street Lower, Dublin 2</string>
    <string name="the_east_side_tavern_directions">From College Green (Trinity College), turn to face Dame Street. Turn left and walk down Nassau Street. Take the first right turn and walk all the way up Dawson Street. Then, turn left and walk around St. Stephen\'s Green. Turn left onto Leeson Street Lower and you will immediately see the East Side Tavern.</string>

    <string name="the_exchequer">The Exchequer</string>
    <string name="the_exchequer_address">3 Exchequer Street, Dublin 2</string>
    <string name="the_exchequer_directions">From College Green (Trinity College), turn to face Dame Street. Then, turn left and walk straight towards Grafton Street. Walk a few feet up Grafton Street and take the first right turn onto Wicklow Street. Walk up this street continue onto Exchequer Street. You will see The Exchequer at the end of this street on the right hand corner.</string>

    <string name="the_garage_bar">The Garage Bar</string>
    <string name="the_garage_bar_address">Essex St East, Dublin 2</string>
    <string name="the_garage_bar_directions">From O\'Connell Street, walk over O\'Connell bridge and turn right onto Aston Quay. Walk straight until you come to the Ha\'penny bridge. Continue on straight until you come to the Millennium bridge. Then, turn left onto Eustace Street and turn right onto Essex Street East. You will see the Garage Bar a few feet up on the right.</string>

    <string name="the_george">The George</string>
    <string name="the_george_address">George\'s Street, Dublin 2</string>
    <string name="the_george_directions">From College Green (Trinity College), turn to face Dame Street. Walk up this street and take the third left turn onto South Great George\'s Street. Walk a few feet up this street and you will see The George on the right.</string>

    <string name="the_gingerman">The Gingerman</string>
    <string name="the_gingerman_address">39 Fenian Street, Dublin 2</string>
    <string name="the_gingerman_directions">From College Green (Trinity College), turn to face Dame Street. Turn left and walk around Trinity College. Continue straight onto Nassau Street, then onto Leinster Street South. At the end of this street, turn left onto Lincoln Place. Walk up this street and continue onto Fenian Street. You will see The Gingerman on the left.</string>

    <string name="the_globe">The Globe</string>
    <string name="the_globe_address">11 South Great George\'s Street, Dublin 2</string>
    <string name="the_globe_directions">From College Green (Trinity College), turn to face Dame Street. Walk up this street and take the third left turn onto South Great George\'s Street. Walk a few feet up this street and you will see The Globe Bar on the left.</string>

    <string name="the_grafton_lounge">The Grafton Lounge</string>
    <string name="the_grafton_lounge_address">2 Duke Lane Upper, Dublin 2</string>
    <string name="the_grafton_lounge_directions">From College Green (Trinity College), turn to face Dame Street. Turn left and walk up Grafton Street. Take the first left turn onto Duke Street. Then, take the first right turn onto Duke Lane Upper. You will see The Grafton Lounge a few feet down on the left.</string>

    <string name="the_grand_social">The Grand Social</string>
    <string name="the_grand_social_address">35 Lower Liffey Street, Dublin 1</string>
    <string name="the_grand_social_directions">From O\'Connell Street (the Spire), turn to face O\' Connell bridge and walk straight. Take the first right turn onto Abbey Street Lower. Walk up this street and take the first left turn onto Liffey Street Lower. Walk up this street and you will see The Grand Social on the right.</string>

    <string name="the_gypsy_rose">The Gypsy Rose</string>
    <string name="the_gypsy_rose_address">5 Aston Quay, Dublin 2</string>
    <string name="the_gypsy_rose_directions">From O\' Connell Street, walk over O\' Connell bridge and turn right onto Aston Quay. Walk up this street towards the Ha\'penny bridge. You will soon see The Gypsy Rose on the left.</string>

    <string name="the_hairy_lemon">The Hairy Lemon</string>
    <string name="the_hairy_lemon_address">Stephen Street Lower, Dublin 2</string>
    <string name="the_hairy_lemon_directions">From College Green (Trinity College), turn to face Dame Street. Turn left and walk up Grafton Street. Take the first right turn onto Wicklow Street and then take the second left turn onto William Street South. Walk all the way up this street and take the last right turn. You will see The Hairy Lemon on the right hand corner.</string>

    <string name="the_harbourmaster">The Harbourmaster</string>
    <string name="the_harbourmaster_address">1 Custom House Quay, IFSC, Dublin 1</string>
    <string name="the_harbourmaster_directions">From O\'Connell Street (the Spire), turn to face O\' Connell bridge and walk straight. Take the second left turn onto Abbey Street Lower. Walk all the way up this street and around the bus garage (Busáras). Turn right and walk into the IFSC. You will see the Harbourmaster on the left corner.</string>

    <string name="the_liquor_rooms">The Liquor Rooms</string>
    <string name="the_liquor_rooms_address">7 Wellington Quay, Dublin 2</string>
    <string name="the_liquor_rooms_directions">From O\' Connell Street, walk over O\' Connell bridge and turn right onto Aston Quay. Walk straight along the Quays, past the Ha\'penny bridge. Continue on straight, past the Millenium bridge. You will soon see The Liquor Room\'s on the left.</string>

    <string name="the_living_room">The Living Room</string>
    <string name="the_living_room_address">Cathal Brugha Street, Dublin 1</string>
    <string name="the_living_room_directions">From O\'Connell Street (the Spire), turn away from O\' Connell bridge and walk straight. Take the second right turn onto Cathal Brugha Street and you will see The Living Room on the left.</string>

    <string name="the_lombard">The Lombard</string>
    <string name="the_lombard_address">44 Pearse Street, Dublin 2</string>
    <string name="the_lombard_directions">From College Green (Trinity College), turn to face Dame Street. Turn right and walk up College Street. Continue onto Pearse Street. Walk all the way up this street and you will see The Lombard on the left hand corner.</string>

    <string name="the_long_hall">The Long Hall</string>
    <string name="the_long_hall_address">51 South Great George\'s Street, Dublin 2</string>
    <string name="the_long_hall_directions">From College Green (Trinity College), walk straight up Dame Street. Take the third left turn and walk up South Great George\'s Street. The Long Hall is just beyond Fade Street.</string>

    <string name="the_long_stone">The Long Stone</string>
    <string name="the_long_stone_address">11 Townsend Street, Dublin 2</string>
    <string name="the_long_stone_directions">From O\'Connell Street, walk over O\'Connell bridge and continue straight onto D\' Olier Street. Walk up this street and turn left onto Townsend Street. Walk up this street and you will soon see The Long Stone on the left.</string>

    <string name="the_market_bar">The Market Bar</string>
    <string name="the_market_bar_address">14A Fade Street, Dublin 2</string>
    <string name="the_market_bar_directions">From College Green (Trinity College), turn to face Dame Street. Walk up this street and take the third left turn and walk up South Great George\'s Street. Take the third left turn onto Fade Street. You will see The Market Bar a few feet away.</string>

    <string name="the_mercantile">The Mercantile</string>
    <string name="the_mercantile_address">28 Dame Street, Dublin 2</string>
    <string name="the_mercantile_directions">From College Green (Trinity College), walk straight up Dame Street. Continue on past Church Lane and Trinity Street. You will soon see the Mercantile on the left.</string>

    <string name="the_morgan_bar">The Morgan Bar</string>
    <string name="the_morgan_bar_address">10 Fleet Street, Dublin 2</string>
    <string name="the_morgan_bar_directions">From O\' Connell Street, walk over O\' Connell bridge and continue straight onto Westmoreland Street. Take the first right turn onto Fleet Street. Walk a few feet up this street and you will see The Morgan Bar on the right.</string>

    <string name="the_norseman">The Norseman</string>
    <string name="the_norseman_address">28 Essex Street East, Dublin 2</string>
    <string name="the_norseman_directions">From O\'Connell Street, walk over O\'Connell bridge and turn right onto Aston Quay. Walk straight until you come to the Ha\'penny bridge. Continue on straight until you come to the Millennium bridge. Then, turn left onto Eustace Street. Walk up this street and you will see The Norseman on the left hand corner.</string>

    <string name="the_octagon_bar">The Octagon Bar</string>
    <string name="the_octagon_bar_address">8 Wellington Quay, Dublin 2</string>
    <string name="the_octagon_bar_directions">From O\' Connell Street, walk over O\' Connell bridge and turn right onto Aston Quay. Walk straight along the Quays, past the Ha\'penny bridge. Continue on straight, past the Millenium bridge. You will soon see The Octagon Bar on the left.</string>

    <string name="the_odeon">The Odeon</string>
    <string name="the_odeon_address">Old Railway Station, 57 Harcourt Street, Dublin 2</string>
    <string name="the_odeon_directions">From College Green (Trinity College), turn to face Dame Street. Turn left and walk all the way up Grafton Street. Then, turn right and walk past St. Stephen\'s Green. Continue straight onto Harcourt Street. Walk all the way up this street and you will see The Odeon on the left.</string>

    <string name="the_old_stand">The Old Stand</string>
    <string name="the_old_stand_address">37 Exchequer Street, Dublin 2</string>
    <string name="the_old_stand_directions">From College Green (Trinity College), turn to face Dame Street. Then, turn left and walk straight towards Grafton Street. Walk a few feet up Grafton Street and take the first right turn onto Wicklow Street. Walk up this street and you will see The Old Stand across the road on the right hand corner.</string>

    <string name="the_oliver_st_john_gogarty">The Oliver St John Gogarty</string>
    <string name="the_oliver_st_john_gogarty_address">58 Fleet Street, Dublin 2</string>
    <string name="the_oliver_st_john_gogarty_directions">From O\'Connell Street, walk over O\'Connell bridge and continue straight onto Westmoreland Street. Walk up this street and take the first right turn onto Fleet Street. Walk up this street and you will soon see Oliver St. John Gogarty\'s on the left hand corner.</string>

    <string name="the_palace_bar">The Palace Bar</string>
    <string name="the_palace_bar_address">21 Fleet Street, Dublin 2</string>
    <string name="the_palace_bar_directions">From O\' Connell Street, walk over O\' Connell bridge and continue straight onto Westmoreland Street. Take the first right turn onto Fleet Street. You will see The Palace Bar on the right.</string>

    <string name="the_porterhouse_central">The Porterhouse Central</string>
    <string name="the_porterhouse_central_address">45 Nassau Street, Dublin 2</string>
    <string name="the_porterhouse_central_directions">From College Green (Trinity College), turn to face Dame Street. Turn left and walk up Nassau Street. You will see Porterhouse Central a few feet up on the right.</string>

    <string name="the_river_bar">The River Bar</string>
    <string name="the_river_bar_address">1 Burgh Quay, Dublin 2</string>
    <string name="the_river_bar_directions">From O\' Connell Street, walk over O\' Connell bridge and turn left onto Burgh Quay. You will see the River Bar on the right.</string>

    <string name="the_south_william">The South William</string>
    <string name="the_south_william_address">52 South William Street, Dublin 2</string>
    <string name="the_south_william_directions">From College Green (Trinity College), turn to face Dame Street. Turn left and walk up Grafton Street. Take the first right turn onto Wicklow Street and then take the second left turn onto William Street South. Walk up this street and you will soon see the South William on the left.</string>

    <string name="the_stags_head">The Stags Head</string>
    <string name="the_stags_head_address">1 Dame Court, Dublin 2</string>
    <string name="the_stags_head_directions">From O\'Connell Street, walk over O\'Connell bridge and continue straight onto D\'Olier Street. At the end of this street, take a right up to College Green. From there, walk up Dame Street and turn left onto Trinity Street. Turn right onto Dame Lane and you\'ll see The Stag\'s Head up on the left.</string>

    <string name="the_sweeney_mongrel">The Sweeney Mongrel</string>
    <string name="the_sweeney_mongrel_address">32 Dame Street, Dublin 2</string>
    <string name="the_sweeney_mongrel_directions">From College Green (Trinity College), turn to face Dame Street. Walk up Dame Street. Continue on past Church Lane. Continue on past Trinity Street. You will soon see The Sweeney Mongrel on the left.</string>

    <string name="the_temple_bar">The Temple Bar</string>
    <string name="the_temple_bar_address">47 Temple Bar, Dublin 2</string>
    <string name="the_temple_bar_directions">From O\'Connell Street, walk over O\'Connell bridge and turn right onto Aston Quay. Walk straight until you come to the Ha\'penny bridge. Then, turn left and walk under Merchant Arch. You are now in Temple Bar, the Temple Bar is down the cobblestones on the right.</string>

    <string name="the_turks_head">The Turks Head</string>
    <string name="the_turks_head_address">27 Parliament Street, Dublin 2</string>
    <string name="the_turks_head_directions">From O\'Connell Street, walk over O\'Connell bridge and turn right onto Aston Quay. Walk straight until you come to the Ha\'penny bridge. Continue on straight until you come to the Millennium bridge. Then, turn left onto Eustace Street and turn right onto Essex Street East. Walk up this street and you will see The Turk\'s Head on the left hand corner.</string>

    <string name="whelans">Whelans</string>
    <string name="whelans_address">25 Wexford Street, Dublin 2</string>
    <string name="whelans_directions">From College Green (Trinity College), turn to face Dame Street. Walk straight up Dame Street and take the third left turn onto South Great George\'s Street. Walk straight up this street and continue onto Aungier Street. Walk straight up this street and continue onto Wexford Street. You will see Whelan\'s a few feet up on the right.</string>

    <string name="the_woolshed">The Woolshed</string>
    <string name="the_woolshed_address">The Parnell Centre, Parnell Street, Dublin 1</string>
    <string name="the_woolshed_directions">From O\'Connell Street (the Spire), turn away from O\' Connell bridge and walk straight. At the end of the Street, turn left onto Parnell Street. Walk all the way up this street and you will see The Woolshed on the right</string>

    <string name="the_workmans_club">The Workmans Club</string>
    <string name="the_workmans_club_address">10 Wellington Quay, Dublin 2</string>
    <string name="the_workmans_club_directions">From O\' Connell Street, walk over O\' Connell bridge and turn right onto Aston Quay. Walk straight along the Quays, past the Ha\'penny bridge. Continue on straight, past the Millenium bridge. You will soon see The Workman\'s Club on the left.</string>

</resources>
